Digital One Piece
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky.
I believe in tomorrow if we Dorry.
I-I-I-YYYYYYYYY.
хeiy C'mon let's go everybody!
Oh we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on let's go, baby baby.
Oh we share the one dream.
Come on let's go, everybody.
Oh we share the good times.
We share the good times.
Let's go, baby, baby,
always share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see or to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought up by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go everybody!
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top, we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Always share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Always share the one world.
There?
Hey, thanks, lady. You're the best
I can't imagine anyone hating frills.
You men are just too strange!
Yeah, well, whatever you say.
Either way, thanks for taking them off.
Okay, bye for real this time!
I gotta hurry.
Are all men so hasty?
I can't rest till I know my
friend survived like I did.
That's all that matters.
Because as long as they're alive, we
can get back up and keep fighting!
I'm going to get stronger
than all those guys!
Let's do this!
I'll walk all the way back
to Sabaody on my hands!
That'll toughen me up for sure.
Think you could get me a ship?
Wow, you really are hasty.
You don't have any ships?
We're in a calm belt? That's right.
This island lies in an
area known as a calm belt,
and it's surrounded by a
giant den of sea kings.
That's another reason sailors
never dare to come near this place.
Castaways do sometimes make
their way to our shores,
but they almost always do so as corpses.
Wait, but you said your leader
was part of a pirate crew, right?
The ship of our snake princess, the Yuda,
is pulled by two giant
poisonous sea snakes,
so even sea kings don't dare to attack it.
And it's the only ship
on Amazon Lily. Eww!
This sucks!
And there's no wind?
Should I just build a raft
and paddle all the way there?
That's a joke, right?
Hey!
I'll just build a raft and
paddle all the way there!
Wait, you weren't joking?
Yeah! It's done!
But it's already falling apart!
Ah!
I have no obligation to save you.
Do all men sink like a rock
even if they're sailors?
That was close.
Damn it!
If only Franky was here!
I'm screwed!
You're not the only one with problems!
Why did you have to cling to me when you
should have been running away from here?
If this keeps up much longer, I'll
end up growing attached to you!
Hold on! Just stop!
Why do you want to shoot me?
you know come to think of it these arrows
are crazy strong those
girls were chasing me
earlier they were busting
up stone walls with
those things doesn't look
like there's anything
special about them though
well of course these
arrows are strong they're
imbued with our Haki
you're mocking me are to you Haki i never
heard of it there she
is margaret are you safe
you made it the man's with
her strike him down coward
come back forgive me if you were injured
margaret but our situation is quite
dire the snake princess has returned so
we must vanquish this fiend post-haste
yes we did notice the
sea kings thank you the
sea prism stone on this
battleship may conceal
our presence from the
beasts for a while but
after waiting here for
so long they eventually
caught on and attacked
us we would prefer to
avoid such encounters but
as you know the agreement
between the kuja and the
government forbids us
from getting closer than
three kilometers from
So, like fools,
here we are waiting in a monster's nest
while you ladies take your sweet time.
Hey, have you heard?
They say that the ruler of the Kuja is
a monster that can turn people to stone.
That's stupid.
You killed that sea king?
Well, you can color me impressed.
Those of us who travel on the Grand Line
are no strangers to these creatures.
But the ones here in the Calm Belt are
certainly larger and
decidedly more ferocious.
No way!
Our cannons didn't even
leave a mark on that thing!
Look, guys!
He's alive!
Monster though it may be, if I allowed
that beast to devour a marine vessel,
How could I call myself a vice-admiral?
I am not here to hunt sea
kings or to chat about them.
Let us conduct our business quickly
so that I may leave these waters.
Your words are as sharp as your blade.
Then hear them well, Kuja pirates.
I tire of waiting here.
I am Vice Admiral Momonga
of Navy Headquarters.
Warlord of the Sea and
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock.
I have come for you.
Reveal yourself.
The Snake Princess does not
cater to your beck and call.
There's your answer, you
might as well go home now.
Look at those ugly men,
I'm sophisticated Ford.
I haven't seen a live one in a long time.
Whenever pirates or merchants see the
Kuja flag flying above the island,
They play in terror.
That laugh isn't very ladylike.
We received a message from your princess.
She claimed that she would
reply to our summons.
But now it appears she
was not quite sincere.
This morning's paper.
A place and date has been decided.
For the public execution of Portgas D.
Ace The second division commander
of the whitebeard pirates.
There is no turning back now!
The world government has
issued strict orders.
That the seven warlords
of the sea assemble.
Refuse and our agreement will become void?
and your princess's title
as warlord will be revoked.
Do you hear me?
Boa Hancock!
Which one of you had the audacity
to place this kitten in my path?
My deepest apologies, Empress.
Thanks for full responsibility.
You should be more careful.
Yes, of course.
Stop it.
At long last, Bower Hancock.
Careful, men.
Keep your guard up.
That's the pirate Empress?
She's the most beautiful
woman in the world.
So, you've come for me at last.
Stubborn and meddlesome, I see.
I shall be frank.
I have no intention of keeping my promise.
In other words, I refuse
to go to war for you.
Still, I rather like my position as a
warlord, so I think I shall keep it.
Also, you shall give me all the cargo
on your ship quickly without complaint.
That's enough!
I won't stand for you
acting like a spoiled child!
Do you honestly think we'll
accept such unreasonable demands?
Haul it over, men!
I'll do anything you want.
Order me around some more.
Put that cargo down this instant
or I'll throw you overboard!
Sorry, I couldn't resist her, sir.
Porcus Deace's public execution
will be exactly one week from today.
The event will be held in the
town square of Marineford.
In other words, we're doing this
inside of Navy Headquarters itself.
There is no doubt that Whitebeard will
attempt to rescue him in the next few days,
likely with the strength of
his entire crew behind him.
Under the leadership of three admirals,
and with the aid of the
seven warlords of the sea,
Navy Headquarters is determined
to stop him at any cost.
Will you give up the title of
warlord or accept your orders?
Make your decision quickly.
You've kept us waiting long enough!
I already told you I like being a warlord.
However, I loathe the world government.
I have no interest in
following their orders.
Surely I can find a better solution.
Oh, I know.
How does this sound?
The Marines who came to escort
me had a mysterious accident.
When they were discovered,
they had all been transformed into
stone and were promptly disposed of.
She's planning to do something.
Don't let your guard down!
I've heard about Hancock doing this before
a merchant ship was attacked by the Kuja
pirates and when it was discovered later
There weren't any crew members on board.
Just a bunch of weird statues.
Those aren't people are they?
You mean they were all turned to stone
I've had enough of these threats your
temper tantrums will not be tolerated.
Do you hear me?
Our big sister has a rotten personality,
but in the end she always
gets her way Indeed.
And there's a very good reason for that.
Would you like to know why?
Because no matter what I do, even if I kick
a kitten, even if I yank off your ears,
why, even if I were to commit
murder, the world would forgive me.
And that is because, yes, it
is because I am beautiful.
You're right you can abuse me all you
want your highness stop that you fools!
The guilty thoughts swimming in your
hearts shall turn your flesh to stone.
Love love be?
Oh, I'd expect no less
from a Navy Vice Admiral.
Clever, forcing the wicked
thoughts from your mind with pain.
I do applaud your conviction, though I
can't extend that compliment to your men.
They should be ashamed.
Now you're the only one left.
But one is not zero.
We shall return to our
peaceful home of Amazon Lily.
Aye, aye, Snake Princess.
Listen up, Boa Hancock.
I won't turn away.
I refuse to return empty-handed.
Unless you reappear in two days,
your position will be revoked.
Do as you wish.
Open the gate!
The snake princess has returned!
We missed you!
Welcome home, Kashi Pirates!
We're glad you're back!
We love you, snake princess! Yes!
Looking good, Ron! Yes, Daisy!
We brought back lots of moves!
They're so awesome!
I'm gonna join the pirates when I grow up!
It's the Gorgon Sisters!
I love you, Snake Principal! Daisy!
Welcome back, Princess.
We've prepared a monkey carriage for you.
Is there anything to report? No.
Everything's fine.
Iron ore, gunpowder,
alcohol, and northern crops.
What a truly impressive haul.
Yeah, we plundered a couple of
merchant vessels in one pirate ship.
Not to mention the loads
of cargo we claimed from.
a central government ship.
You Kashi Pirates really are
a force to be reckoned with.
It's
on the way to the castle now.
Ron, did you collect any
books? Grignion. Books, huh?
Oh, we did appropriate a recent newspaper
off the central government ship.
Here, all yours.
Welcome back, snake princess.
We're so glad to have you home.
Snake princess, me too.
It's nice to be back!
Initiative, what is this?
Oh, I forgot.
The children of the village,
lovingly crafted a statue of your
likeness out of clay as a gift.
It's endearing.
How much love and labor they
poured into its creation!
It took them forever to
bring it up to the castle.
Because it would break if they dropped it.
Don't you think it's cute?
It's me.
But made out of mud.
Snake princess!
Don't bring such filth into the castle?
It's inelegant!
Throw it away at once and clean the floor.
I'm curious, Anishita.
Oh? About?
I couldn't help but
notice the city defenders
were absent from the
wharf upon our arrival.
Uh, actually,
you see, a ferocious and violent monkey
came rampaging out of the jungle.
The size and brute strength of
the beast was simply astonishing.
So everyone has left for
the jungle to hunt it.
I see.
It's no concern.
They'll be back shortly.
I'm truly sorry they
weren't there to greet you.
No matter.
Well then, would you care for a drink?
Why'd sake?
Go ahead and make that
two while you're at it.
Granny Moon, how nice of you
to defile my private chambers.
Oh, I didn't see you come in.
How did you get in here?
Forget how I'm here.
Get rid of her.
Hold on!
Listen, Snake Princess!
You forgot, please.
Now say it.
Please listen, Snake Princess.
I have just learned that there's a ship
from Central anchored off our shores.
They've come here with the express
purpose of summoning you, have they, Nyot?
The Central Government has
ordered you into active duty.
That's right they want me to go to war.
Why are you here?
You must go You must uphold the
agreement or they'll revoke your title.
I know you've just returned But surely
you still have the strength to fight I?
Do?
But I'm afraid to go.
Oh, she's like a weird old puppy.
Wait, I'm not sorry for that!
I don't really think you are.
Now, think this through!
All that is truly protecting our
nation is your title as warlord.
Our greatest deterrence
from outside forces?
Is Amazon Lily's location.
Here in the Sea King riddled
waters of the Calm Belt.
But as time marches
forward, so does technology.
And now these central dwellers have ships!
That provide them with safe
passage through these parts.
We need a new weapon to keep them at bay.
Your rank as warlord is the sole
reason they avoid our shores,
despite the activities
of the Kuja pirates.
Think of your people.
Our island is home to
helpless children and elderly.
If you lost your title, Amazon Lily
would just be another nation of pirates,
and the government would bring ruin to us.
Now you're the one who
sounds like she's afraid.
I am old.
I could drop dead at any moment.
Gaze into this crystal
ball and see your future.
I shall conjure an image of your fate.
Yo.
You idiot.
Throw her out.
Right now.
Yes, of course, Snake Princess.
Wait, hear me out.
That's so rough.
I listen respectfully and
you treat me like a fool.
Did you think I'd fall for your chicanery?
Your reign here ended well
over three generations ago.
How dare you act like you're
still the empress of Amazon Lily?
Gloriosa.
It doesn't matter what I do.
I could lay waste to every
inch of this nation of ours.
On a whim.
And still, I would be forgiven
because I'm beautiful.
Amazing!
She looks down on people
so much that she looks up!
Why on earth should I listen
to the words of a disgraced
ruler who abandoned her people
to journey the outer seas?
Traitor to the Kuja!
So I live alone in penance
on the outskirts of town!
Which is where you should
be at this very moment.
Do not presume to tell me what to do.
I'm the reigning empress!
Say princess!
Put me down already!
That said, I can't help but
admire your overwhelming passion.
You may be right
You agreed to my request.
Thank you for understanding
the needs of your people.
How wonderful
So how soon will you be leaving
never know your place fool? You!
Now get out of my sight!
I'll curse on you, Snake Princess!
Snake Princess, you threw
an old woman out the window!
An accident?
Oh, of course!
We know it wasn't your fault!
Granny Neon?
I may be old, but I'm
still a Kuja warrior.
My skills haven't withered a bit.
Your attention, please.
The Snake Princess will now bathe.
You must evacuate the castle now.
Hey, come on, we've got to go.
What?
I just sat down.
I'm still eating.
Come on, hurry, everyone.
Sounds like it's bath time.
Get ready, girls.
They're clearing out the castle now.
It's about to get packed in here.
For the next several hours,
no one is allowed to enter the
castle under any circumstances.
Why is it such a big deal when
the universe takes a bath?
Everyone acts like we're
going to war or something.
First things first, how old are you?
Eight years old.
Well, then I think I can tell you.
Wait, you don't mean the secret.
That's right.
You see, the Gorgon was a monster.
It stalked the tides
of the central oceans.
If anyone made the mistake of gazing
upon this horrifying creature.
They would be turned to stone.
After facing countless perils
along a treacherous journey.
The snake princess and her sisters encountered
the monster and managed to slay it.
But the screams of the dying abomination?
were laced with evil, and it
placed the sisters under a curse.
The penetrating eyes of the monster were
etched across the flesh of the sisters'
backs.
So they remain forever
staring, even today.
And if anyone gazes
upon these wicked eyes,
their body will harden into
stone, and they'll die.
That's why the Gorgon sisters refused to
remove their clothing before another human.
As a matter of precaution they always
post guards when they bathe and
they secure and evacuate the castle
did you see where he went yeah he
ran up the side of the mountain you
don't think he could be headed back
to the village do you i thought he
was bound and determined to find a
ship okay now what's
next wait a sec Margaret
did say they've got a pirate ship i wonder
how hard it'd be to
borrow it that won't
work nami's not here
i'd get lost in no time
without her i got it all i gotta do is ask
someone for a ride in their ship wherever
they're going i'm sure they won't mind a
quick trip to Sabo Outta
so who am i gonna ask
for a ride probably gotta
be someone important
and high up and if they're high up that
means they gotta live in a tall building
right my head's on fire
from all this thinking
right guess i'll just try the first tall
building i can find we
need to hurry by this
point the snake princess
has probably returned
we'll be in trouble if she finds the man
what was that the roof of
the castle tower collapsed no
this is bad that's where where
the empress is taking a bath!
It's real shallow!
I'm safe!
This is...
a huge bath!
Oh man, hey, that thing on your back?
It looks kind of familiar.
You saw it?